<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>pixelbar</title>
 <link href="http://pixelbar.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://pixelbar.github.io/"/>
 <updated>2015-12-22T23:53:08+01:00</updated>
 <id>http://pixelbar.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Pixelbar</name>
   <email>bestuur@pixelbar.nl</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Succesfully funded</title>
   <link href="http://pixelbar.github.io/2015/12/22/funded/"/>
   <updated>2015-12-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://pixelbar.github.io/2015/12/22/funded</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Recently, we made a proposal for funding at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.citylab010.nl/plannen/hackerspaceinrotterdam&quot;&gt;CityLab 010&lt;/a&gt; (Dutch). Furthermore, we gave a pitch to the city council and other related parties to inform them about the situation in Rotterdam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re happy to announce that the Rotterdam government has passed this grant towards our cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be wondering why a hackerspace would reach out to the government in the first place. As a hackerspace we have certain goals we’d like to make happen sooner than later. This oppertunity has brought us closer to our goals without sacraficing the membership fee of our members, which makes us more flexible to make decisions and basically gives us a better runway for the first year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still have questions? Just &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#098;&amp;#101;&amp;#115;&amp;#116;&amp;#117;&amp;#117;&amp;#114;&amp;#064;&amp;#112;&amp;#105;&amp;#120;&amp;#101;&amp;#108;&amp;#098;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#108;&quot;&gt;reach out&lt;/a&gt; to us.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introducing Pixelbar</title>
   <link href="http://pixelbar.github.io/2015/12/19/introducing-pixelbar/"/>
   <updated>2015-12-19T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://pixelbar.github.io/2015/12/19/introducing-pixelbar</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Starting 2016, Rotterdam will officially have a proper hackerspace: Pixelbar. We’ve been a small community and are prepping a workspace in &lt;a href=&quot;http://stadshavensrotterdam.nl/deelgebieden/merwe-vierhavens/&quot;&gt;M4H&lt;/a&gt;. It’s time to meet, socialize and collaborate in 010. Bring your knowledge and ideas about computers, machinery, tech, science, digital art and let’s get this party started!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-do-we-offer&quot;&gt;What do we offer?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to our workspace, we bring a few other things to the table:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Awesome members that would like to meet you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work with you on projects and explain how we’ve build a few of our own on our &lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.pixelbar.nl/index.php/Main_Page&quot;&gt;wiki&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn you more through e.g. &lt;a href=&quot;/workshops&quot;&gt;workshops&lt;/a&gt; and make them accessible for anyone that wants to learn.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Give you insight on our code using &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/pixelbar&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit (local and international) hackathons and other hackerspaces together.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;strong&gt;☰&lt;/strong&gt; to see more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-can-i-do&quot;&gt;What can I do?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe you’re already familiar with the hackerspace community, or maybe you’re not. You might have heard of us through a friend, or about us on the news. Either way, the thing you should know is hackers come in many forms: from food- to IKEA-hacking and obviously computer-hacking too. Everything is possible, as long as you share that information - you’re a hacker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If that’s the case, you’re welcome to join us by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/register&quot;&gt;Become a member of the space and start hacking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/register&quot;&gt;Become a friend of the space to support our cause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a great - hacking -  year!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video id=&quot;gif-mp4&quot; poster=&quot;https://media.giphy.com/media/k8kG3Plo87Aqs/200_s.gif&quot; style=&quot;margin:0;padding:0&quot; width=&quot;391&quot; height=&quot;219&quot; autoplay=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;https://media.giphy.com/media/k8kG3Plo87Aqs/giphy.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
  Your browser does not support the mp4 video codec.
&lt;/video&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
